A Guide to the Papers of the Low Moor Iron Company
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Records
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C-M", incl. Cargill; Manhattan Rubber Co.; Crager System - specialist at marketing stock issues; Manufacturers Record - right wing reactionary pamphlet, 1910 Sept. -1922 Dec.; (2 folders) (Box Box 189)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C-G", incl. Cargill correspondence; B. F. Goodrich; Timber & Rubber Companies, 1912 Sept. -1915 April (Box Box 189)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "B", incl. Burnley Bros.; Burlingham Coal, 1913 April -1914 April (Box Box 189)
  - H. A. Dalton - treasurer; Cargill; transfers mostly, 1922 Jan. -Dec. (Box Box 189)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M", incl. Means, Cargill correspondence; A. Ersking Miller - coal; Davis-Payne Produce, 1910 May -1922 Nov. (Box Box 189)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M", incl. purchasing agent Matthew Addy & Co.; McDonald Lumber Co.; C. & O. Railroad - for coal; assistant treasurer correspondence; Mitchell & Dillion - coal; Miller Supply Co., 1908 April -1914 June; (2 folders) (Box Box 190)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "L-M", incl. E. C. Means, Cargill; McAllister & Bell - Low Moor sells coal; W. J. Loth Stove Co. - Low Moor sells iron, 1909 Feb. -1914 May (Box Box 190)
  - Lynchburg Foundry, incl. E. C. Means, general Manager; orders, terms, prices, problems, sales, 1910 June -1913 Dec.; (2 folders) (Box Box 190)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-L", incl. S. G. Cargill Co.; Harry O. Locher, Sr. - river sand for furnace, 1910 June -1912 June (Box Box 190)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "P-U", incl. Cargill, Treasurer; Puritan Machine Co.; G. T. Thayer trustee for Potts Creek; U. S. Rail Co., 1908 Dec. -1915 March (Box Box 191)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-B", incl. Ayers; Baldwin Locomotive Co., 1914 April -1914 Dec. (Box Box 191)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "D", incl. S. G. Cargill; Commercial Coal Co., 1915 Jan. -April (Box Box 191)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "D", 1914 Nov. -1915 April (Box Box 191)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "E-F", 1904 Feb. -1915 Feb. (Box Box 191)
  - Elmore Mfg. Co., 1909 May -1913 May (Box Box 191)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "W" incl. Walter Wallingford & Co. Whipple Co.; Weir Frog Co., 1904 (Box Box 191A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-T", 1921 March -1922 Dec. (Box Box 192)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Am-Co, Li-Lo", 1910 Dec., 1913 March -1914 June (Box Box 192)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "H-W", 1922 Jan. -Dec. (Box Box 192)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "H-S", 1922 Jan. -Dec. (Box Box 192)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-P", 1921 Jan. -1922 Jan. (Box Box 192)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-C", 1921 Dec. -1922 Dec. (Box Box 192)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A, C, H, I", 1922 Jan. -Dec. (Box Box 192)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-H", 1914 March, 1922 Jan. -Dec. (Box Box 192)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Tl", incl. S. G. Cargill, 1915 May -1917 June (Box Box 192)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "H-L, R", 1912 -1914 (Box Box 192)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from Ashland Iron & Mining Co. to TL, 1912 Sept. -June 1914 (Box Box 192)
  - Lobdell Car Wheel Co. and Lodge & Shipley, Machine Tool Co. to TL, 1910 March -May 1913 (Box Box 192)
  - Link-Belt Co. to TL, 1910 June -1913 Sept. (Box Box 192)
  - Ashland Fire Brick Co. letters, 1913 Jan. -Dec. (Box Box 192)
  - Lynchburg Foundry Co. miscellaneous correspondence, 1912 Jan. -1914 Aug.; (2 folders) (Box Box 193)
  - Liondale Iron Co. miscellaneous correspondence, 1914 Jan. -Dec., 1913 Dec. (Box Box 193)
  - Lidgerwood Mfg. Co. miscellaneous correspondence, 1910 Feb. -1913 Nov. (Box Box 193)
  - Harry O. Locher Co. miscellaneous correspondence, 1913 Jan. -Feb., 1914 Feb. -Nov. (Box Box 193)
  - Business letters "A-W", 1917 Sept. -Dec., 1918 May -Dec., 1908 Dec. (Box Box 193)
  - C. & O. Coal & Coke Co. business letters, 1911 Jan. -Dec. (Box Box 193)
  - Business letters "A-L", 1910 -1918 (Box Box 193)
  - Business letters "B-N", 1915 Nov. -Dec., 1916 May -Dec. (Box Box 194)
  - Business letters "B-K", 1915 June -Sept., 1908, 1910, 1914 (Box Box 194)
  - Business letters "C-R", 1915 Feb. -Oct., 1916 Jan. -March (Box Box 194)
  - Business letters "C-P", 1914 Sept. -1917 Feb. (Box Box 194)
  - Business letters "I-S", 1916 March -Sept., 1926 Sept. -Dec. (Box Box 194)
  - Business letters "A-S", 1915 Jan., 1926 March, 1924 June -Aug. (Box Box 195)
  - Business letters "A-M", incl. correspondence with Frank Lyman, 1915, 1916, 1924; (2 folders) (Box Box 195)
  - Business letters "A-Y", 1915, 1916, 1921, 1926, 1927; (2 folders) (Box Box 195)
  - Business letters "C-T", 1921, 1927 (Box Box 195)
  - Business letters, mostly from steel, iron and coal companies, 1916, 1917, 1926, 1927 (Box Box 196)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "P", incl. Princess Furnace, Phillips Isham Pig Iron & Coke, Providence Life, Pocahontas Coal, 1915 -1916, 1924; (2 folders) (Box Box 196)
  - Low Moor Iron Co. intra-company correspondence, 1915, 1916, 1926 (Box Box 196)
  - Business letters "B-N", incl. Amos Klotz New River Silica Co.; J. W. Bell, 1926, 1927 (Box Box 197)
  - Business correspondence, mostly from and to Frank Lyman, 1916 (Box Box 197)
  - Business correspondence, largely with Walter Wallingford and Phillips Isham, 1915, 1916, 1924, 1926 (Box Box 197)
  - Business correspondence, largely with C. & O. Railroad and Phillips Isham & Co., 1924, 1925 (Box Box 197)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C", incl. Cabell Coal Co., 1925, 1927 (Box Box 197)
  - Business correspondence "C-R", incl. Covington Machine Co.; Rand Drill Co Republic Iron & Steel; Emerman Co.; B. A. Dalton, 1921, 1922 (Box Box 198)
  - Business correspondence "B-R", incl. Hunter B. Frishkorn, Federal Finance Co.; Bradstreet Co.; Browning Co., 1914, 1922 (Box Box 198)
  - Business correspondence "A-I", 1913 -1915 (Box Box 198)
  - Business correspondence "A-P", incl. Carbon Fuel Co.; Atlas Powder Co.; Lehigh New England Railroad Co.; Phillips Isham, 1914, 1922 (Box Box 198)
  - Business correspondence, mostly with Carey Machinery & Supply Co., 1912 -1913 (Box Box 198)
  - Business correspondence "A-W", incl. Charles F. Avery; Duzets & Sons; Covington Machine Co.; Speyer & Sons, 1915 -1917; (2 folders) (Box Box 199)
  - Business letters "D-T", 1916 -1917 (Box Box 199)
  - Inventory Store #11, 1919 (Box Box 199)
  - Business letters "B-E", incl. Dupont Co.; Dalton, treasurer; Evans Coal Co.; Eastern Coal & Export Corp., 1916 -1917 (Box Box 199)
  - Business letters, mostly from and to Covington Machine Co., 1915 -1917 (Box Box 199)
  - Business letters "C-R", incl. H. A. Dalton, College of Charleston, Columbia University, Phillips Isham, 1908 -1918 (Box Box 200)
  - Business letters "B-T", incl. Dalton Nash & Co.; Nash-Isham & Co.; H. A. Dalton & Co.; Maurice Desseau, 1907 -1923 (Box Box 200)
  - Business letters from Nash, Isham & Co., 1909 -1912 (Box Box 200)
  - Business letters, mostly from Walter Wallingford and Nash, Isham, 1907 -1909 (Box Box 200)
  - Business letters "D-P", incl. W. J. Loth Stove Co.; Phillips-Isham, 1907 -1919 (Box Box 200)
  - Business letters, mostly from and to Phillips Isham, 1919 (Box Box 200)
  - Business letters, mostly from and to Dalton, Nash & Co., 1901 -1904; (3 folders) (Box Box 201)
  - Business letters, incl. U.S. Dept. of Labor; Prestolite; New Jersey Zinc Co, 1918 -1919 (Box Box 201)
  - Business letters "A-S", incl. Stephenson-Adamson Co.; Chester A. Phillips; Suffolk Feed & Fuel, 1916 -1918 (Box Box 201)
  - Business letters "S-Y", incl. Standard Oil Co.; Standard Slag Co.; Weld & Liddell, 1925 (Box Box 201)
  - Business letters "E-R", 1925 (Box Box 202)
  - Business letters and internal communication, 1925 (Box Box 202)
  - Business letters, mostly from Thomas A. Mack & Co., 1902 (Box Box 202)
  - Business letters, incl. Thomas Mack; Nash-Isham; article on the decline of Virginia Pig Iron Industry, 1909 -1925 (Box Box 202)
  - Business correspondence, incl. New River Coal Co.; Berwind White Coal Mining Co.; Brigh & Gill, Suppliers; H. A. Dalton, Treasurer, 1925 -1926 (Box Box 202)
  - Business correspondence "B-V", incl. Virginia Iron Coal & Coke Co.; Bewind-White Co., 1925 (Box Box 202)
  - Business letters from coal companies, incl. Low Moor Iron Co. Coal Dept.; White Oak Coal Co., 1903 -1915 (Box Box 203)
  - Business letters "E-K", 1919 (Box Box 203)
  - Business letters "B-Z", incl. Zelnicker Co.; Low Moor Iron Co. - intracompany correspondence; C. & O. Railroad; Phillips Isham, 1924 (Box Box 203)
  - Business letters "C-N", incl. Graselli Chemical Co.; H. A. Dalton Co., 1916 (Box Box 203)
  - Business letters, mostly to C. & O. Railroad, 1915 -1925 (Box Box 203)
  - Business letters, contains some material on company owned theaters; some Phillips Isham letters, 1914, 1926 -1927 (Box Box 204)
  - Business letters, mostly "B, L, M", 1926 -1927 (Box Box 204)
  - Business letters, mostly Walter Wallingford, 1919 -1927; (2 folders) (Box Box 204)
  - Business letters, heavy equipment, 1919 (Box Box 204)
  - Blast records for Kay Moor Mines, 1917 (Box Box 205)
  - Business letters, mostly Nash-Isham & Co., 1908 -1911 (Box Box 205)
  - Business letters "N, W", incl. Walter Wallingford; E. H. Wilson & Co.; Nash-Isham & Co., 1908 -1921 (Box Box 205)
  - Business letters "U-W", incl. E. H. Wilson Co.; Underwood Typewriter Co., 1921 (Box Box 205)
  - Business letters, incl. electric equipment companies, 1925 (Box Box 205)
  - Business letters "T", incl. Thomas Motor Car Co.; Times Square Auto Co., 1915 -1916 (Box Box 205)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "B-R", 1909 -1920 (Box Box 206)
  - Business letters "A", 1909 -1920 (Box Box 206)
  - Business letters "A-P", 1920 (Box Box 206)
  - Business letters, incl. Miller Supply Co.; Klotz Bros. Co., 1916, 1920 (Box Box 206)
  - Business letters, Mitchell & Hotchkiss, 1915 -1916 (Box Box 206)
  - Business letters "M-S", 1915 -1916 (Box Box 206)
  - Business letters, Lunkenheimer Co., Klotz Bros. Co., 1916 -1919 (Box Box 207)
  - Business correspondence - Morris, Wheeler & Co. and The Moore Lime Co., 1916 (Box Box 207)
  - Business correspondence "M-V", 1910 -1916 (Box Box 207)
  - Business letters "L-W", incl. Lettsome & Co.; Leschen & Sons - rope; Old Dominion Iron & Nail Works, 1915 -1916 (Box Box 207)
  - Business letters "A-N", incl. New York Machinery Exchange; E. M. Nettleton & Co.; New River Hardware Co.; Austin Nicholls & Co.; H. A. Dalton, treasurer, 1915 -1917 (Box Box 207)
  - Business letters "D", incl. John T. Delaney; Davis & Blake, 1917 (Box Box 207)
  - Furnace reports, 1920 (Box Box 208, 209)
  - Business letters "F-W", 1910 -1913 (Box Box 208, 209)
  - Business letters "M-W", 1911 (Box Box 208, 209)
  - Business letters "V", incl Vulcan Co., 1908 -1913 (Box Box 208, 209)
  - Business letters "B-I", 1920 -1921 (Box Box 208, 209)
  - Business letters "C-H", 1921 (Box Box 208, 209)
  - Business letters "L-R", 1921 (Box Box 208, 209)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and list of tonnage produced at various places, 1912 -1913 (Box Box 210)
  - Business letters, mostly from Westinghouse, 1907 -1921; (2 folders) (Box Box 210)
  - Business letters "C", 1921 (Box Box 210)
  - Miscellaneous letters "C, W", incl. Covington Machine Co.; Crane Co. Craft Bros.; Westinghouse Co., 1913 -1921 (Box Box 210)
  - Business correspondence "C-S", 1921 (Box Box 211)
  - Business correspondence, incl. Walter Wallingford & Co.; Standard Oil Co.; L. O. Bightbill; Nash-Isham & Co., 1913 (Box Box 211)
  - H. A. Dalton - treasurer correspondence, 1925 (Box Box 211)
  - Business letters "A-C", incl. Corn Exchange Bank, 1925 (Box Box 211)
  - Business letters "B-C", 1925 (Box Box 211)
  - Business letters "H-I", incl. Illinois Pipe Mfg. Co., 1921 (Box Box 211)
  - Business letters, some from Henry R. Worthington, 1909 -1911 (Box Box 212)
  - Business letters "Williams", incl. Williams Barnett; David Williams Co., 1912 -1913 (Box Box 212)
  - Business letters "V-W", incl. Virginia Hot Springs Co.; George T. Wickes, 1912 -1913 (Box Box 212)
  - Business letters from Virginia Portland Cement Co., 1909 -1921 (Box Box 212)
  - Business letters, great mixture, 1923 -1925 (Box Box 213)
  - Business letters "A-W", 1925 (Box Box 213)
  - Business letters "A-D", incl. American Ore Reclamation; Corn Exchange Bank; Covington National Bank, 1925 (Box Box 213)
  - Business letters from H. A. Dalton, 1925 (Box Box 213)
  - Business letters, H. A. Dalton, Wickes Bros. & White Oak Coal Co., 1910 -1925 (Box Box 213)
  - Business letters "W-Z", incl. Wyatt Coal Co.; B. A. Zacks & Sons; Yale & Towne Mfg. Co.; Winifrede Coal Co., 1911 -1913 (Box Box 213)
  - Business letters "C-T" and some correspondence from Low Moor Coal Dept, 1921 (Box Box 214)
  - Business letters and Low Moor Iron Co. Coal Dept. correspondence, 1921 (Box Box 214)
  - Business letters, including letters from Standard Oil and IRS, 1921 -1925 (Box Box 214)
  - Business letters "C", incl. Corn Exchange Bank and Covington National Bank, 1919 -1925 (Box Box 214)
  - Business letters, incl. Banks Supply Co., Huntington, West Virginia, 1921 (Box Box 214)
  - Business letters "A-T", incl. American Wiping Cloth Co.; Earle C. Bacon; Alexander Milburne Co.; Taylor Wharton Iron & Steel Co., 1912, 1921 (Box Box 214)
  - Business letters, incl. Virginia Tax & Corporation Commissions, and bills in the state Senate pertaining to business regulation, 1910 (Box Box 215)
  - Business letters "Virginia", incl. ICC Freight Rate Case, Virginia Pig Iron Assoc.; Virginia Coal & Coke Co., 1913 (Box Box 215)
  - Business letters "I-N", incl. New River Coal Operators Assoc.; National City Bank, 1921 (Box Box 215)
  - Business correspondence, mostly from Phillips Isham, 1921 (Box Box 215)
  - Business letters "P-W", incl. Low Moor Quarterly Report of the Mines (Jan. - March 1917), 1921 (Box Box 215)
  - Proposal for boiler system, Hagam Corp., Pittsburgh, Pa., 1924 (Box Box 215)
  - Letters principally from Otis Elevator Co., Republic Iron Co., Queen City Supply Co., 1900 (Box Box 216)
  - Letters (miscellaneous), mostly from and to J. C. Fowle, 1900 -1906 (Box Box 216)
  - General correspondence, incl. War Industries Board, 1917 (Box Box 216)
  - Fuel Administration, incl. some material on coke allocation, 1917 -1918 (Box Box 216)
  - General business correspondence "L-P, V", incl. Low Moor Iron Co.; Metropolitan Life Insurance Co.; Virginia Iron Coal & Coke Co., 1919 (Box Box 216)
  - General business correspondence, incl. Guaranty Trust Co. of New York, New River Coal Operators Assoc., 1919 (Box Box 216)
  - Business letters "C-H", incl. Joseph C. Hunter; C. & O. Railroad; C. J. Hutter & Co., 1910 -1913 (Box Box 217)
  - Business letters from C. & O. Railroad and Nash Isham, 1908 -1920 (Box Box 217)
  - Business letters "H-S", incl. Horwitz Co.; Iron Trade Review; Standard Oil Co., 1910 -1920 (Box Box 217)
  - Business letters "I-V", incl. Travelers Insurance Co.; Walter Wallingford Co. Phillips-Isham Co., 1909 -1920 (Box Box 217)
  - Business letters "B-G, T", incl. Travelers Indemnity Co.; Greenville Car Co.; Gauley Mountain Coal Co., 1920 (Box Box 217)
  - Business letters "H-P, V", 1920 -1922 (Box Box 217)
  - Business letters "L-M", incl. Linde Air Products Co.; Lawrenceville Bronze Co. Lynchburg Iron & Steel Scrap Co.; Lumberman's Credit Assoc., 1925 (Box Box 218)
  - Miscellaneous letters "A-M", incl. Abrahams & Co.; Manhattan Rubber Goods & Co.; MacWhyte Co.; Mount Hope Insurance Agency; Bowling Green Business University, 1925 (Box Box 218)
  - Scales, 1924 (Box Box 218)
  - Miscellaneous letters "I", and Low Moor intra-company correspondence, 1925 (Box Box 218)
  - Miscellaneous letters, Low Moor intra-company correspondence, Charleston Electric Co., 1925 (Box Box 218)
  - Letters - Zelaick Crayon Works, West Virginia Rail Co., Weir Co., George D. Whitcomb Co., 1915 -1916 (Box Box 219)
  - Letters - large number to and from Woodrow-Bradley Co., 1915 -1920 (Box Box 219)
  - Walter Wallingford letters, 1924 -1925 (Box Box 219)
  - Letters - mostly from and to New River Coal Operators Assoc. with some information on labor conditions in coal mines as seen through management, 1925 (Box Box 219)
  - Miscellaneous letters "K-L", incl. Lake Superior Iron Ore Corp.; Hon. F. W. King, 1925 (Box Box 219)
  - Miscellaneous letters "L", incl. Low Moor Iron Co. Blast Records; Frank Lyman; Charles Loxey - President of Princess Furnace Co., 1925 (Box Box 219)
  - Business letters, mostly from Southeastern Iron Corp., 1917 -1919 (Box Box 220)
  - Miscellaneous letters "H-P", incl. Harvard Alumni Assoc.; Helmick Foundry Machine Co.; Iron Trade Products Co.; Pulaski Foundry & Mfg. Co.; Charles Parsons, 1919 -1920 (Box Box 220)
  - Business letters, miscellaneous correspondence "P", mostly to and from Princess Iron Corp.; Peckitt, President of Empire Steel & Iron Co., 1916 -1919 (Box Box 220)
  - Business letters from Norfolk & Western Railroad, New River Coal Operators Assoc., 1917 -1919 (Box Box 220)
  - Output agreements for WWI and C. & O. Railroad letters, 1919 (Box Box 220)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C", incl. some material dealing with fuel and Navy contracts - WWI; Coal Run Coal Co.; Conference Committee on National Preparedness, 1918 (Box Box 221)
  - Low Moor correspondence from and to H. A. Dalton and E. M. Cabell, chief clerk, 1918 (Box Box 221)
  - Business letters "D-H", incl. H. A. Dalton, Eimer-Amend; The Dictaphone; Eastern Coal & Export Corp., 1918 (Box Box 221)
  - Miscellaneous letters "E-I", incl. Erie Steam Shovels; Hattenstate Steam Shovels; Interstate Corp., 1917 -1918 (Box Box 221)
  - Business letters, mostly from and to IRS; Payne & Hamilton Law offices, 1918 (Box Box 221)
  - Letters to/from F. W. King (lawyer), 1916 -1919 (Box Box 222, 223)
  - Letters to/from Phillips Isham Co., 1925; (2 folders) (Box Box 222, 223)
  - Letters to/from Standard Oil Co. and Steele & Payne Co. - grain, etc., 1915 -1916 (Box Box 222, 223)
  - Letters to/from Worthington Hardware Co. and Wyoming Shovel Works, 1915 -1916 (Box Box 222, 223)
  - Business letters "W", incl. What Cheer Coal Mining Co.; Wick Wire Bros.; Wiggins Co.; Worthington Steam Pump Co., 1915 -1916 (Box Box 222, 223)
  - Letters - C. M. Shanahan (contractor), Cleveland - Cliffs Iron Co., Connelly Iron Sponge & Governor Co., Goodyear Tire & Rubber Co., 1916 -1917 (Box Box 224)
  - Stock received, 1918 -1919 (Box Box 224)
  - Material on Low Moor employees in WWI, 1918 (Box Box 224)
  - Business letters, mostly from/to H. A. Dalton, Treasurer of Low Moor, 1918 (Box Box 225)
  - Business letters, incl. Dalton; Ashland Iron & Coal; Ashland Firebrick, 1917 -1918 (Box Box 225)
  - Miscellaneous letters "B", incl. Blancke Co.; Barlow Co., 1917 -1918 (Box Box 225)
  - Business letters "B" and U. S. Labor Dept, 1918 (Box Box 225)
  - Business letters "Iron & Steel", incl. material from American Iron & Steel Inst. on production statistics and production figures for pig iron in 1919, 1918 -1920 (Box Box 225)
  - Miscellaneous letters, incl. Mr. H. Firmstone; War Industries Board; Empire Iron & Steel Co., 1916 -1919 (Box Box 225)
  - Walter Wallingford & Co. - pig iron, 1908 (Box Box 225)
  - Business letters "C" and "C. & O. Railroad", incl. Chicago Pneumatic Tool Co.; Clifton Forge National Bank; Clifton Forge Milling & Feed Co., 1918 -1919 (Box Box 226)
  - Miscellaneous letters "C-G", incl. Covington Machine Co., 1918 (Box Box 226)
  - Business letters from/to H. A. Dalton and miscellaneous correspondence "B-C" incl. Buffalo Steam Pump Co., 1918 (Box Box 226)
  - Letters to/from Phillips Isham, 1919; (3 folders) (Box Box 226)
  - Business letters, advertising, coke, employment, 1919 -1920 (Box Box 227)
  - Business letters, material involving coke rate cases, 1917 -1918 (Box Box 227)
  - Coke rates, iron ore rates, and furnace reports, 1917 -1919 (Box Box 227)
  - Correspondence mostly from Low Moor Operators Assoc., meeting reports, 1918 -1919 (Box Box 227)
  - Summary of pig iron contracts, 1918 -1919 (Box Box 228)
  - Daily Furnace Reports, 1919 (Box Box 228)
  - Weekly stock reports on amount of Low Moor iron on hand, 1919 (Box Box 228)
  - Princess Iron Corp. letters, 1920 -1921 (Box Box 228)
  - Letters and pig iron quotations, 1917 -1918 (Box Box 228)
  - Navy Dept. and Iron & Coal Exchange, 1919 (Box Box 228)
  - Letters from/to American Ore Reclamation Co., 1914 -1919 (Box Box 228)
  - Letters to/from Phillips Isham, 1918 -1919; (2 folders) (Box Box 229)
  - Letters to/from Wright Phillips Co.; Virginia Portland Cement Co.; Virginia Iron, Coal & Coke Co., 1916 -1919 (Box Box 229)
  - Virginia Pig Iron Assoc. and Virginia Sales Agency, incl. production figures on Virginia Pig Iron (1918-1919), 1916 -1919 (Box Box 229)
  - Letters to/from several coal companies, incl. Cox Bros. Coal; Maryland Coal Co.; New River Coal Co.; Cumberland Coal Co.; Business Service Coal Co.; C. G. Blake Coal Co., 1925 (Box Box 230)
  - Letters, mostly regarding pig iron prices also including Low Moor medical health records of employees, 1925 (Box Box 230)
  - Letters mostly concerned with pig iron and coke prices, 1925 (Box Box 230)
  - Letters concerned with conditions of the iron market pricing, 1925 (Box Box 230)
  - Large number of hardware orders, 1900 -1915 (Box Box 231)
  - Business letters "S", some regarding replacement parts; also including Scullin Steel Co.; L. W. Sherwood; Simmons Hardware Co., 1900 -1916 (Box Box 231)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "V-W" most letters deal with machinery, iron and timber purchases, incl. Watkins-Cotrett Co.; Virginia Slag Corp., 1915 -1916 (Box Box 231)
  - Business letters "T-V", incl. Tidewater Cement Co., 1915 -1916 (Box Box 231)
  - Most material deals with coke ovens, coke sales, and coke purchases, 1917 -1919 (Box Box 231)
  - Analyses of iron ore, ca. 1920 (Box Box 231A)
  - Ore sellers, incl. William Muller & Co.; Shimer & Co.; Ogelbay-Norton Co.; Davidson Ore Co.; Cleveland Cliffs Iron Co.; Debbevoise-Anderson Co.; Allegheny Ore Co.; M. A. Hanna & Co.; J. T. McAllister, 1925; (4 folders) (Box Box 231A)
  - Iron ore sellers and Bureau of Mines, 1917 -1919 (Box Box 231A)
  - Phillips Isham letters, incl. U. S. Railroad Administration, 1916 -1920; (2 folders) (Box Box 232)
  - Virginia Western Power Co.; U.S. Employment Service; Dalton, Nash & Co. pig iron, coke, 1906 -1919 (Box Box 232)
  - Miscellaneous letters and Dalton, Nash & Co., 1906 -1912; (2 folders) (Box Box 232)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C-D" and Covington National Bank statements, incl. Corrigan McKinney Co.; Dupont Co., 1906 (Box Box 232)
  - Business letters "D", incl. Dominion Engineering Co., 1906 (Box Box 232)
  - Walter Wallingford & Co. - pig iron and coke, 1921; (2 folders) (Box Box 233)
  - Business letters, Covington Machine Co., Director General of Railroads, miscellaneous "B", 1918 -1920 (Box Box 233)
  - Miscellaneous letters and letters to/and from war industries agencies, 1918 -1920 (Box Box 233)
  - General business and labor department correspondence; labor laws; some material on conditions in the iron business, 1918 (Box Box 233)
  - Manganese ore, 1918 -1919 (Box Box 233)
  - Inventory, incl. Store #9, Kay Moor, West Virginia, 1919 June -1924 Dec.; (3 folders) (Box Box 234)
  - Inventory Store #2, 1922 June (Box Box 234)
  - Inventory, 1918 Dec. (Box Box 234)
  - Inventory Store #11, 1917 June (Box Box 234)
  - Inventory Store #8, 1918 June (Box Box 234)
  - Inventory Store #9 Kay Moor, West Virginia, 1920 Dec. -1922 Dec.; (3 folders) (Box Box 234)
  - Inventory, 1922 (Box Box 234)
  - Daily Low Moor furnace labor report, 1920 -1921 (Box Box 234)
  - Inventory Store #12 Fayetteville, West Virginia, 1920 Dec. -1921 Dec.; (2 folders) (Box Box 234)
  - Inventory Store #11 Kay Moor, West Virginia, 1920 Dec. -1923 June; (3 folders) (Box Box 234)